[Music]
Johnny okay
Carter I can stay here all night so why
don't you and I cut the crap and you
tell me what happened on March
15th and what's in it for Carter Finley
what's in it for you is I don't send you
back to
jail
the guy's name is cat branchman I met
him downtown at a club called the
clutching kitten you may have heard of
it it's down on the corner of hang and
Fur Street cat
branchman so what's a guy like you and a
guy named
cat
okay I know what you're doing Finley
you're just using what you see in my
poster I'm not detective I'm telling the
truth we'll see how much truth you tell
after a few weeks in solitary conf fine
detective you've twisted my arm that's
better the guy's name wasn't cat
branchman it was a Chinese guy named Mr
meow he's the real gang
boss story went he hung guys from trees
and took pictures of them Finley used to
run a club downtown a front of course
called it the paulw and poster Finley
ran it with a guy named Hong
inar
okay let's try this one more
time
Finley who do you work
for
um coffee Mr
Coffee
Coupe coffee cop his name was baly tall
man coffee cop now you're just talking
about me Finley I'm going to give you
one more
chance who is in charge his name was
angry
man the warehouse is located in the
diploma for being a detective I want a
name Justin thank you hang tree don't
say hang godamn it do not say
hang hang nope hangman Justin cat Finley
poster do not say poster or
cat cat poster okay that's it I'm I'm
losing my patience winlow get this
out of
[Music]
here I'm losing my
patience let's try this one more
time getting too old for
[Music]
this
well played
Detective well played
indeed hey
Carter you hang in
[Music]
there I am here with oaz buck the rookie
out of Stanford
University that's the one welcome to C
Class
and the racist ass Melly Gibson know I
know pretty much Stimpy now hold on a
second Mr T someone slapping around your
little
[Music]
homie oh God damn forget about the tele
prom I need to speak from the
heart shut the up folks I'm sorry I'm
going to get everybody tonight I'm going
to nobody is saying who is
next do
gifts is is still kind
[Music]
of